我们有一件小事想让你知道
There's a small matter we wanted to make you aware of.
曾在游轮公司担任会计的詹姆斯·韦塞尔
Former cruise employee, James Wiesel in accounting,
翻译　水平有限的皮带断了
好像被官司吓到了 而且...
seems to have gotten spooked. And...
字　　幕　　侠
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
后期　Jason肖　特效　小布
ZIMUXIA.CN
看上去他有可能要开口了
seems like he might be about to talk.
校对　水平有限的皮带断了　时间轴　iiichiii
我还以为我们把这一切都解决了呢
I thought we had this all sewn up.
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
压制　Jason肖
-我说的是希望如此  -不要...打断我
-I said I'd hoped. -Don't... Interrupt me.
监制　水平有限的皮带断了
ZIMUXIA.CN
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
你跟你爸谈过注入大笔投资
Have you talked to your dad about a major injection
甚至是将我们私有化吗
or even taking us private?
这事我们之间就可以谈
It's a conversation we can have.
敬比尔 有史以来最好的老板
To Bill, the best boss that ever lived.
我要做个文档给你
So I'm gonna create a word document for you,
然后我打印给你 因为我不想任何纸质材料上
and then I'm gonna print it because I don't want anything
留有我的笔迹
with my handwriting on it.
我认为瑞亚很危险 而且我认为我们必须阻止她
I think Rhea is dangerous, and I think we need to stop her.
我们需要抛开个人恩怨 来一次家庭休战
We need to put feelings aside and call a family truce.
那 我们向韦塞尔先生提出了第二次
So we made the second threat-slash-offer
恩威并施的提议 他拒绝了
to Mr. Wiesel, and he said, "No."
新人会被撕成碎片
The new face is gonna get ripped to shreds.
我真的在想瑞亚的问题 我看她看准了吗
I really am wondering about Rhea. Have I got her right?
她最合适
She's the one.
我将任命瑞亚·贾瑞尔
I shall be appointing Rhea Jarrell
作为我的集团总裁
as my Chief Executive Officer.
这个狗屎帝国 是时候偿还一切了
This empire of shit, time to pay up.
晚上好 我是苏珊·瓦尔迪
Good evening. I'm Susan Vardy,
今晚重点报道 独家专访
and in focus tonight, an exclusive interview
韦斯达·罗伊科集团举报者詹姆斯·韦塞尔
with Waystar Royco whistleblower James Weissel.
性剥削 暴力 盗窃
Sexual exploitation, violence, theft,
此外 还有许多其他罪行 全部隐藏在
plus, a host of other crimes, all of it hidden
掩盖与腐败之下
by cover-ups and corruption
-以避免负面新闻  -滴答滴答
-to avoid damaging headlines... -Cha-ching.
-黑幕 黑幕  -我们的嘉宾指控
- Book deal, book deal! -That's what my guest
上述现象在"明亮星" 美国第二大
alleges went on for decades inside Brightstar,
游轮运营公司 内部存在了数十年
America's second-largest cruise line operator.
那 詹姆斯 您在明亮星见证了一些可怕的事情
So, James, you witnessed some terrible things at Brightstar.
最让您感到困扰的是什么
What disturbed you the most?
嗯 苏珊...
Well, Susan...
"好吧 苏珊 我是个垃圾
"Well, Susan, I'm a piece of shit.
-我是黄鼠狼 我很害怕 "  -明亮星游轮是一个
-I'm a weasel, and I'm scared." -Brightstar Cruises was,
几十年来 管理不善的大粪坑……
for decades, a cesspool of mismanagement...
数十年来支付了数百万美元
and millions and millions of dollars paid out over decades
以掩盖由明亮星的员工提供的
to cover up sexual exploitation and harassment
性剥削和性骚扰 其中很多事情
by Brightstar employees, and a lot of it
实际上是由当时的负责人莱斯特·麦克林托克犯下的
actually committed by the man in charge, Lester McClintock.
-莫叔叔  -莫·麦克林托克
-Uncle Mo. -Mo McClintock.
谁能忘了我们的老莫
Who could forget our Mo?
而且 还有更严重的事件
Then you have even more serious incidents
发生在美国管辖范围之外
occurring outside of U.S. Jurisdiction.
来宾落水 受伤 以及原因不明的死亡
Guests overboard, injury, and, uh, unexplained deaths.
那您怎么看待这些事件
And what are you saying about these incidents,
包括乘客落水这样的情况
including passengers overboard?
-我什么都不知道  -噢
-I don't know everything. -Oh!
他现在什么都不知道了
He doesn't know everything now.
但是 我知道故事的内容
But I know what the stories were,
而且我很清楚 没有任何...
and I do know that there was no appetite...
证据在哪里 露丝
Yeah, where's the proof, Ruth?
...高层管理人员有意向
...whatsoever from the senior management
去揭露真相
for uncovering the truth.
是谁在支持你 黄鼠狼 嗯
Yeah, who's backing you, weasel? Hm?
-你是说有人在掩盖这些事吗  -绝对的
-You're saying there were cover-ups? -Absolutely.
还有那些人 下船的人 公司总部的人
And people, people off the ship, the company HQ,
他们知道正在进行这种掩盖吗
did they know this sort of cover-up was going on?
好吧 公司确实有一些人在负责监管 嗯...
Well, there was there a certain amount of oversight, um...
格丽·科尔曼...
Gerri Kellman...
-格丽  -韦斯达的总顾问格丽·科尔曼
-Gerri! -Gerri Kellman, the Waystar general counsel.
-格丽警报  -...她说 要优先考虑
-Gerri alert! -...saying no bad PR
-没有糟糕的公关  -耶 格丽
-was the priority. -Yeah, Gerri!
嗯 高级管理人员应该受到保护
That, um, senior management was to be protected.
这种情况一直持续到比尔·洛克哈特改变了局面
And that went on until Bill Lockheart changed things up.
-哇 老比尔  -比尔·洛克哈特是当时的
-Wow! Old Bill! -Bill Lockheart was the then-head
-公园和游轮部门的负责人  -去他妈的比尔
-of parks and cruises. -Fuck Bill.
是的 在比尔的领导下 公司进行了大整治
Yeah, there was a clean up under Bill and
他向肯德尔·罗伊述职
he reported to Kendall Roy.
我们遇到比尔的时候 我很喜欢他
I liked Bill when we met him.
-肯  -你知道吗 他们试图整治公司
-Ken! -You know, they tried to clean things up.
然后 最近 汤姆·万布斯甘斯...
And, uh, recently, Tom Wambsgans...
万布斯甘斯
Wambsgans!
我相信他做了很多收尾工作
I believe he tied off a lot of loose ends.
嘿 了不起的汤姆
Hey, bangin' on the Tom-Tom!
但是稍微深入一点细节
But getting into the details a bit.
-厉害啊 汤姆  -不
-Woo, Tom! -Nope.
你的爸爸妈妈应该为此感到骄傲
Your mom and dad should be so proud.
你提到的这个...
You mentioned this...
...短语
...phrase
在影子日志中多次出现过
that occurred many times in the shadow logs.
-噢 "影子日志"  -事件 NRPI
-Ooh, "Shadow logs"! -Incident: NRPI.
嗯...意思就是 嗯...
Uh... Yeah, that's, uh...
无真人参与
No Real Person Involved.
嗯 那是什么意思
Uh-huh, and what does that mean?
就是说 是一个性工作者
That means it's a sex worker
或者是外国港口的移民工人
or a migrant worker at a foreign port,
不涉及客人或固定员工
not involving a guest or a permanent member of staff.
无真人参与
No real person involved.
-那这些影子日志...  -噢 我再也看不下去
-And these shadow logs... -Oh, I can't watch any more of
这该死的扯谈了
this fucking bullshit
...完整地记录了这些罪行
...with the full record of these crimes.
给你 康纳
Here you are, Connor.
-你知道日志在哪吗  -不知道 不知道 我...
-Do you know where they are? -No. No, I--
爸 你没事吧
Dad, you okay?
太扯谈了 很明显 是桑迪在支持他 很明显
It's bullshit! Clearly, Sandy's backing him. Clearly.
与他的搭档 还有他的六家他妈的空壳公司
With his buddy and his six fucking shell companies.
他妈的什么都说什么都干的狗混蛋
Sick bastards who'd fucking do and say anything.
但是 你不觉得我们应该看吗
Don't you think we should watch, though,
这样我们才能回应
so we can have a response?
我他妈出钱请了50个人在看这个狗屎
I've got 50 fucking people paid to watch this shit.
高级管理人员的责任是管理好...
It's senior management's duty to be in control...
我不需要看这个废话 我们晚点再看
I don't need to see this nonsense. We'll watch it later.
...公司雇用的人员
...of the people it employed.
他们要么很清楚内情 这样就太可怕了
Either they did know, which is terrible,
或者他们根本不知情 这样的话 就是不合理的...
or they didn't know, which is an unconscionable...
-缺乏控制  -嗯
-lack of control. -Uh-huh.
韦斯达公司的代表拒绝露面...
Waystar representatives declined to appear...
-嗯  -...不过 他们发表了一份声明说
-Uh-huh. -...but they did issue a statement saying,
-"我们很失望..."  -好的 谢谢你告诉我
-"We are disappointed..." -Okay, thanks for letting me know.
" ...你们播放了
"...you have given airtime
这些加工过的 而且已经被揭穿的声明..."
to these recycled and debunked claims..."
操
Fuck!
很...糟糕 很糟 不过...
So... bad. Bad. But, uh...
嗯 不过还不算糟透了
Yeah, but not too bad?
很糟 我觉得 非常糟
Bad, I think. Very bad.
我认同 很糟
I would agree. Bad.
嗯 很明显 这他妈很糟 弗兰克
Yeah, obviously, it's fucking bad, Frank,
我们是在这里讨论具体有多糟
we're talking here about how bad.
好吧 从公关的角度来看 我不希望任何人
Well, just from a PR perspective I wouldn't want anyone
低估这件事的糟糕程度
to underplay how bad it was.
这些是我们要攻击的谈话要点
These are the talking points that we're hitting.
他带着怨恨
He's embittered.
他是个掩盖自己劣迹的坏人
He's the bad guy covering his tracks.
没有证据 没有受害者的发言 也没有什么新鲜的内容
No proof, no victim voices, and nothing that new.
想听听我的想法吗
Want to hear what I think?
我觉得我们说出真相
I think we say the truth.
这里的高级管理层和家族成员
That the senior cadre here, and the family,
对此一无所知
knew nothing of this.
所以我们抛弃莫 老莫是个坏苹果
So we throw Mo overboard. Mo, bad apple.
黄鼠狼詹姆 也是个坏苹果
Jim Weasel, bad apple.
秘密进行内幕交易 私下串通 得到了桑迪和斯图威
Spies a book deal. Sotto voce, backed by Sandy and Stewy,
全是公司的鬼把戏 没什么大不了的
all corporate fuckery, no real concern.
就以往的烂事而言 恐怕我们得拿比尔当炮灰
And in terms of historic shit? I'm afraid we give up Bill.
因为他应该让我们知道他的发现
Because he should have let us know what he discovered,
而不是在不告诉我们的情况下进行公司整治
rather than clean up without telling us the details.
我觉得 除了比尔
I don't think there's gonna be paper
不会有别的文件了
that shows anything beyond Bill.
嗯
Yeah.
我的意思是 每个人都喜欢比尔 但是...
I mean, everyone likes Bill, but...
-我喜欢比尔  -我是说 比尔试图进行整治
-I like Bill. -I mean, Bill tried to clean up.
我喜欢比尔
I like Bill.
不过 看起来牺牲比尔就能降压 对吧
It seems like Bill is where the buck stops, though, right?
继     承
第 二 季  第９集
我们牺牲比尔吗
Do we kill Bill?
是的
Yeah.
那...
So...
我想我刚刚拒绝了10亿美元的四分之一份额
I think I just, uh, turned down a quarter of a billion dollars.
是的 我要...我要喝一杯
Yeah, I'm gonna-- I'm gonna make a drink.
嗯...我想...我想我得...
Uh... I think-- I think I'm gonna...
我...我可以喝这些酒 对吧
I-- I can drink these drinks, right?
这些是给人喝的酒吧
These are drinks for people?
看样子票务销售可能会略有上升
Looks like there might be a slight uptick in ticket sales.
因为洛根...答应他会照顾我的 所以...
'Cause Logan... promised he'll look after me, so--
-放弃十亿的四分之一份额吗  -嗯
-A quarter of a billion? -Mm-hm?
-相反 你信任我爸  -怎么了
-Instead, you're trusting Dad? -What?
不 我是说
No, I mean,
我爷爷经常改变主意 所以这不是最终决定
my grandpa changes his mind a lot, so it's not final.
而且 嗯 他很健壮
And plus, um, he's so sturdy.
所以 天知道我可能要等多久
Like, who knows how long I might have to wait.
总之 我很好 因为 呃...
I'm good, anyway, 'cause, uh...
我的...那 我刚刚和我妈通话 她说
My-- So, I was just talking to my mom, and she said,
显然 他无论如何都会留五百万给我
apparently, he'll leave me five million anyway,
所以我还是很有钱 宝贝
so I'm golden, baby.
五百万屁都干不了 格雷格
You can't do anything with five, Greg.
五百万就是个噩梦
Five's a nightmare.
嗯...是吗
Mm-- Is it?
嗯 是的 既不能退休 又不值得去工作
Oh, yeah. Can't retire, not worth it to work.
噢 没错 五百万会让你有点神经小错乱
Oh, yes. Five will drive you un poco loco
我可爱的好朋友
my fine feathered friend.
美国最穷的有钱人
Poorest rich person in America.
世界上最高的矮人
The world's tallest dwarf.
马戏团中最弱的大力士
The weakest strongman at the circus.
没错
Mm-hm.
好了 汤姆 嘿 我们搞定了 我们有策略了 进来吧
Okay, Tom? Hey. We're done, we have a strategy, come on.
噢 好的
Oh, okay.
-嘿 汤姆 你很出名  -嘿
-Hey, Tom. You're famous. -Hey.
那 这和之前纽约杂志的文章没有什么区别
So, this isn't that different from the magazine piece.
策略是 我们让比尔来承受
The strategy is, we're letting Bill take it.
一直追溯到比尔 牺牲比尔
It went as far as Bill. Kill Bill.
48小时后就会平息
It'll blow over in 48 hours.
呃...不行
Uh... Well, no.
我刚打完电话 这样绝对不行
I'm just off the phone, and it's definite.
不管是吉尔还是吉莉亚德 都会要求举行听证会
Either Gil or Gilliard are going to call for hearings.
-噢 我操 什么  -等一下 什么
-Oh, fuck. What? -Wait a minute. What?
是的 参议院商业委员会 众议院也可能会提出
Yeah, Senate Commerce. Probably House, too.
工作人员正聚在一起商量如何策划听证会
The staff are huddled on how to choreograph,
但是访谈之后 他们会想快速立法
but after the interview, they'll want to fast track
并将其纳入他们正在筹划的
and roll it into the tourism regulatory hearings
-旅游监管听证会 所以...  -是的 系好安全带吧 伙计们
-they're cooking up, so... -Yup, buckle up, folks.
我们会被邀请去一趟"国家公厕"
We're going to get an invite to the great national latrine.
看看谁想在那里公开拉屎
See who wants to take a public dump.
是的 完蛋先生要去首都了
Yeah, Mr. Fuck is going to Washington.
不 我现在不能出这种事
No! I can't have this now!
他说得对 谁 嗯...他们想要谁去参加听证
He's right. Who, um... Who will they want to testify?
嗯...他们会...他们会想要爸爸去
Uh... Well, they'll-- they'll want Dad.
好吧 现在...但是我们不会接受的
Okay, now... But we won't accept that.
保护好卵泡
Protect the egg chamber!
卡罗丽娜 打几个电话
Karolina. Make some calls.
我们的各种朋友 呃...佛罗里达一伙的
Our various friends. Uh... The Florida gang.
看看谁能阻止这件操蛋的事
See who can jam this the fuck up.
嗯
Right.
我想说 为了弄清真相...
I mean, to actually get to the bottom of this...
...我们可以说 我们有人
...we could argue it would be better
在运作调查 这样会比较好
to have people who operationally--
我们建议... 格丽和汤姆
We suggest... Gerri and Tom?
什么
What?
你想解释一下你的想法吗 雨果
You want to explain your thinking, Hugo?
听着 我...我只是在假设 好吗
Look, I-- I'm just positing here, okay?
好的 嗯 但是你朝着我假设 所以...
Sure, yeah, but you're positing in my direction, so...
是的 只不过是因为总顾问这个位置很有说服力
Yeah, it's just that General Counsel is very compelling,
而且你知道该怎么降压
and you know where the buck stops.
好吧 但是为什么要汤姆
Right. And why Tom?
汤姆可以谈运作 他在那次采访中
Tom can speak operationally. And he got quite heavy play
表现很好 汤姆会很好的
in that interview. Tom would be good.
好吧 我...我...我明白你的想法从何而来了 雨果 显然
Well, I-- I-- I see where you're coming from, Hugo, obviously,
我很乐意帮忙
and I'd be happy to help.
我们也许可以让听证会慢下来
We might be able to slow it down
但是民主党 他们会快速推进
but the Dems, they are gonna push fast,
-他们会对洛根施加压力  -我们可以说"去他妈的"吗
-and they're gonna push Logan. -Do we just say "Fuck 'em"?
去...他妈的国会吗 罗曼
Fuck... Congress, Roman?
是的 小西 去他妈的国会 我让你感到震惊了吗
Yes, Shiv. Fuck Congress. Have I shocked you?
嗯...还有两个半星期就要召开股东大会了
Uh... Shareholder meeting in two-and-a-half weeks.
我的意思是 我们这个时候特别容易受到
I mean, we are unusually subject to the vicissitudes
公众舆论的影响
of public opinion.
嗯...我能翻译 这是弗兰克表达"我们完蛋了"的方式
Uh... I can translate. That's Frank for "We're fucked."
我需要你的帮助
I want your help.
噢 是吗
Oh, yeah?
需要有人去商店买烟吗
Someone needs to run to the store for smokes?
这个讨论会持续一整晚...但是不一定能有对策
This'll go on all night... but it might not be okay.
不一定能有对策
It might not be okay?
国会听证会会把股东吓傻
Congress will spook shareholders.
我现在如坐针毡
I'm on a knife's edge.
在华盛顿的聚光灯下亮相十分钟 最多这样了
Ten bad minutes on camera in D.C., that could be it.
没了
The end.
没了 不是吧
The end? Come on.
我需要你去找主权财富基金
I need you to chase down the sovereign wealth money.
好的 嗯 呃...我的意思是...这是...
Okay. Right. Uh... I mean, that's-- It's, uh...
这是个好主意
It's a cool idea,
但时这个任务有点难 你知道吧
but it's kind of a stretch, you know?
中亚那个家伙的资金
That Central Asian money,
那个没有附带条件 是可以拿来随便玩的干粉灭火器
that's no strings, fuckable dry powder.
现在先把上市公司
Time out from the responsibilities
应该承担的责任忘了
of being a public company.
那就是一条他妈的救生索 你能做到吗
That's a fucking lifeline. Can you do it?
-我可以做到吗  -嗯
-Can I do it? -Uh-huh.
呃...
Um...
操 爸 我...我想说是的
Fuck. Dad, I-- I want to say yes,
但是 老实说 如果这事真的很重要
but I'll be honest, if it's, like, really important,
我的意思是 我可以说我能做到 你知道的
I mean, I can say I can do it, like, you know,
就像是电影里的消防员
a fireman in a movie,
-但是说实话 我...  -你扮演关节的角色
-but honestly, I-- -You act the fucknuckle,
但是你知道吗 大家喜欢你
but you know, people like you.
这是真的去搞定一个大交易
It's a really big fucking deal to set up.
不 任何人都可以做交易
Nah, anyone can do a deal.
这不过是从适当的人那里拿到适当的钱
It's getting the right number from the right suit.
把你的鸡巴强插进去很容易
Getting your dick in there is easy.
让他们心甘情愿上床很难
Getting them into bed, that's hard.
对某些人来说是这样
For some.
你能做到的
You can do it.
嗯...是的
Then, uh... yeah.
当然 爸爸 我明白了
Sure, Dad, I got it.
-随时报告进展  -好的
-Keep me close. -Okay.
让莱尔德和卡尔和你一起...谈细节
Take Laird and Karl... for the details.
好的 我现在就办 噢 还有...
Great, I'm on it. Oh, um, also...
只是为了...我不知道 了解一下
just to... I don't know, check,
呃 玛西娅 她是...在楼上 还是...
uh, Marcia? Is she... upstairs, or--
这样好吗 你还好吗
Is that okay? Are you okay?
你有没有谁可以谈谈这些...
Do you have someone that you can speak to about...
屁事
shit?
你想让我跟心理医生谈谈吗
You want me to speak to a shrink?
你知道吗 你可能想忽悠你妈
You know, you may want to screw your mother,
不过 我在心理方面还行 谢谢
but I am okay in that department, thank you.
好的 我们可以谈谈这些事情 这样很好
Great, well, it's just nice that we can talk about these things.
我要走了
I'm gonna go.
-你好  -嘿 你好吗
-Hello. -Hey, you okay?
嗯 挺好 出发去亚洲 搞定100亿美元的投资
Oh, yeah. Great, yeah. Off to Asia to get ten billion.
-别等我了 再见  -嗨 你怎么样
-Don't wait up, bye! -Hey, how you doing?
嗯 在担心自己同意了担任
Yeah. Worried I've agreed to be CEO
一艘被点燃的死亡海盗船的总裁 你呢
of a dumpster fire pirate death ship. You?
嗯 不担心 坐 坐
Yeah. Not worried. Sit. Sit.
对
Right.
杂志是一码事 但是 这件事
The magazine was one thing but, uh, this?
我不知道他会站出来
I didn't know he was gonna pipe up.
噢 我觉得我是你的预防针
Yeah, I feel like I'm your prophylactic.
防止你滑倒的橡胶垫 这样我就可以保护你
A rubber you've slipped on so I can protect you.
瑞亚 那不是我的想法
Rhea, that was not the idea.
我可以看到我在这一点上发挥了有益的作用
I can see I fulfil a useful role at this point:
一种更体面的风格...
a more respectable flavor...
确保不可靠的股东的投票
secure votes from shaky shareholders.
你很厉害 新的扫帚 你很宝贵
You're good. A new broom. You're golden.
做新的新娘真有意思
It's fun to be the new bride.
重新布置单身汉的公寓
Rearranging the bachelor's apartment.
为获得鲜花而努力
Putting flowers out.
只不过 想到你可能会在冰箱里发现一具尸体
It's just not nice to think you might find
这就不太好了 你知道吗 蓝胡子[残酷的丈夫]
a corpse in the freezer, you know, Bluebeard?
瑞亚 他们没告诉我这事
Rhea, they kept this from me.
-那不过是个无耻的精神病人 相信我  -嗯
-It's a rogue sicko. Trust me. -Uh-huh.
嗯 那...
Yeah. Uh-huh. Well...
不管是偶然还是有意
By accident or design,
你都只给了我很少的回旋余地
you have left me very little room to maneuver.
我可以...去露露脸吗
Shall I... show my face?
噢 那样我会不胜感激
Oh, that would be very much appreciated.
-瑞亚  -小西
-Rhea. -Shiv.
哇 艰难的夜晚
Wow. Tough night.
-真高兴你来了  -好的 谢谢
-Great to have you coming in. -Well, thank you.
想不出任何比你更能帮助我们渡过难关的人了
Couldn't think of anyone better to see us through.
嘿 你们都在这做什么
Hey! What you guys all doing here?
在玩游戏吗
Is there a game on?
-嘿 瑞亚  -说真的...
-Hey, Rhea. - Seriously...
那不过是小题大做
that was a mountain out of a molehill.
每个人都这么说 每天都在举行各种听证会
Everyone's saying it. Hearings happen every day.
给有线电视频道填补空白而已 那 据我了解
C-SPAN filler. So, as I understand it,
我们没有什么好内疚的...
we have nothing to be guilty about...
也没什么好担心的
and nothing to worry about.
所以 是的 我期待着更多的参与
So, yeah. I look forward to, uh, getting more involved.
再见
Toodle-pip!
-谢谢  -他们看起来很害怕
-Thank you. -They look scared.
他们没事
They're good.
瑞亚 我能应付
Rhea, I've got it.
-没什么的  -照顾好自己 好吗
-It's nothing. -Look after yourself, okay?
真高兴见到你 伙计
It's good to see you, man.
而且你知道我有多爱希伯队
And you know how much I love the Hibs.
-该死的赫斯队  -赫斯队
-The fucking Hearts. -Hearts.
-赫斯队  -对
-Hearts. -Yeah.
但是 不管了 我就直截了当地说了吧
But fuck it, I'm just gonna come right out and say it.
好的
Okay.
你觉得有没有可能
Think there's any chance
你们出钱把我们私有化
you guys have the muscle to take us private?
你和你爸对这个想法感兴趣吗
Is that something that's interesting to you and your dad?
-是的  -真的吗
-Yes. -Really?
好吧 这...
Well, that's...
是的 我们有兴趣帮助你们私有化
Yes, we're interested in helping you go private.
是的
Yeah.
我们喜欢把它作为投资组合的一部分
We like it as part of the portfolio,
我们喜欢你们可以分享的新闻专业知识
and we like the news expertise you can share.
-太好了  -好的
-Great. -Okay.
好吧 这太好了
Well, great.
呃...你想...
Uh... You want--
呃...要我给洛根打电话吗 嗯...我应该...
Uh... Shall I call, uh, Logan? Uh... Shall I get--
你能做到吗 罗曼
Can you do it, Rome?
你和你的...
Could you and your, uh...
你的跟屁虫能够来土耳其吗 明天就来
your bum-boys here come to Turkey, like, tomorrow?
-好的...  -向我和我爸推销
-Okay... -And pitch to me and my dad?
当然可以 我们绝对可以来
Absolutely. I think we can absolutely do that.
-对吧 跟屁虫  -嗯
-Ain't that right, bum-boys? -Uh-huh.
在布尔萨举行的阿塞拜疆投资会议
Azeri investment conference in Bursa.
每个人都会去那里 我们可以参加
Everyone will be there, we can get into it.
好吧 那我们他妈的就参加 我可以推销
Well, let's fucking get into it. I can pitch.
-我他妈推销死他们  -嗯
-I'll pitch the fuck out of it. -Mm.
很好 帕迪 踢得不错
Nice, Paddy! Nice!
练习得不错 伙计们 小伙子们都到齐了
Good session, guys. I've got the lads here.
老板们要讲几句话 好吗
The owners are gonna want to say a few words. All right?
练习得不错 伙计们 听好了 星期六的比赛...
Great session, guys. And listen, for Saturday...
你们有能力 你们有精神劲
you have the ability, you have the mentality.
注意不要让自己有压力
Watch that press doesn't leave you exposed
以免造成失误 你们他妈的会赢的 罗曼 说几句吗
on the turnover, and you fucking got this. Rome?
嗯...谢谢 是的 嗯...嗨
Uh... Thank you. Yeah. Uh... Hey.
与你们在一起真的很骄傲
Really proud to be associated with you guys.
嗯...我他妈还能说点什么
Uh... Well, what the fuck can I tell you
你们不知道的呢
that you don't already know?
你们...你们能搞定的 伙计们 不用担心
You-- You got all this, guys. Don't worry about it.
因为你们是一个团队 嗯 当一个团队...
'Cause you guys are a team, and, uh, when a team...
凝聚成一个集体...实际上就无法被击败
is a team... it can't actually physically be beaten.
不可能被击败
It's impossible.
所以 努力点 速度快点 加油 你们这些可爱的混蛋们
So, go hard, go fast, go, you lovely bastards.
-"加油 你们这些可爱的混蛋们"  -我他妈不知道该说什么
-"Go, you lovely bastards"? -I don't fucking know.
我他妈到底该说些什么
What the fuck am I supposed to say?
我完全不知道
I have no idea.
你想让我花20分钟宝贵的时间
Do you want 20 of my best minutes
跟你讲讲土耳其和阿塞拜疆的关系吗
on Turko-Azerbaijani relations?
嗯...什么 关于石油管道合作
Uh... What, the oil pipeline cooperation,
军事和外交联系
the military and diplomatic links,
还是更深层次的文化共鸣
or the deeper cultural sympathies?
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's up?
嘿 爸还好吗 他...他没事吧 他...他正在听证会吗
Hey, how's Dad? Is-- Is he okay? Is he-- Is he doing it?
嗯 是的 我们让他们同意了先让格丽和汤姆上
Uh, yeah, we got them to agree to Gerri and Tom up first,
谈公司运作 然后他与肯再一起上
on operational, and then him with Ken.
把家里的牛卖掉换魔法豆进展如何
How's selling the family cow for magic beans?
噢 是的 是的 是的 就是个笨蛋 一个性害虫
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's right, yeah, just a dipshit, a sex pest
一个在中亚度假的伟大的老笨蛋公爵
and a Grand Old Duke of Dork on a Central Asian vacation.
不 这里没什么可看的 谢谢
No, nothin' to see here, thanks.
噢 我操 是比尔 比尔在这里做什么
Oh, fuck. Bill! What's Bill doing here?
噢 不好了 格丽 如果我们要牺牲比尔
Oh, no! Gerri, if we're gonna kill Bill,
那我不想见到他
I don't want to see Bill.
比尔 嘿 哇
Bill! Hey! Wow.
-比尔  -格丽
-Bill! -Gerri!
-汤姆  -比尔 比尔 比尔 看看你
-Tom! -Bill, Bill, Bill! Look at you!
搞什么呀 你要出席吗
What the fuck? Are you appearing?
-不 天哪 不  -好的
-No! God, no. -Okay.
不 不 嘿 魔术师约翰逊始终是湖人队的
No, no. Hey, Magic Johnson's still a Laker
就算他已经退役了 对吧
even if he's not on the team, right?
是的 没错 对
Yeah, right, okay.
嗯 我住在马里兰州 想着来围观
Ah, I live in Maryland. Just thought I'd come in,
支持一下老伙计们
support the old gang.
嗯 真是够意思 比尔
Well, that's such a nice gesture, Bill.
-很高兴见到你  -嗯
-Great to see you. -Yeah.
我在下面为你们打气
I'm rootin' for ya out there!
去消灭他们吧 我的朋友们
Go get 'em, my friends.
-嗯  -汤姆
-Yeah. -Tom.
-比尔  -格丽 谢谢
-Bill. -Gerri. Thanks.
-祝好运  -哇
-Good luck! -Wow.
-哇  -真是个好人
-Wow. -That's nice.
-太好人了  -我是说 这样真的...很好
-That is nice. -I mean, that is just... nice.
-还是要牺牲他  -再见 比尔
-Still. -Adios, Bill.
是的 安息吧 比利仔
Yeah, rest in peace, Billy boy.
好了 伙计们 好吧 开始了
Okay, folks. All right. Here we go.
"你现在 或者曾经是
"Are you now, or have you ever been,
游轮公司的肮脏的性爱掩盖团伙的一员吗"
a member of the Cruise Dirty Sex Fuck Cover-up Party?"
连线怎么样
How's the link?
我们可以听到你的声音 瑞亚 谢谢
We can hear you, Rhea, thank you.
很好
Great.
-没事 没事 没事  -噢 我的天啦
-Good, good, good. -Oh, my God.
嘿 格丽 你想...我可以再来一遍吗
Hey, Gerri, do you wanna-- Can I do one more?
你想再...再演练一遍吗 还是就一遍就行
Do you wanna do... one more round? Just one?
汤姆 你已经做好准备了
Tom, you've done the prep.
你是被凶手豁免的人 好吗
You are murder-boarded to death, okay?
我知道 我知道 我知道
I know, I know. I know.
你能别焦虑了吗 你害得我都焦虑了
Can you stop angsting? You're angsting me.
-好的 好的  -你只需要记住
-Okay. Okay. -Just remember,
这里不是法院
it is not a courthouse.
只是个舞台 好吗 什么事都会发生 阻扰议事的进行
It is a stage. Okay? Anything goes. Filibuster.
你发言的每一分钟 都是在盗窃他们的时间
Every minute you're speaking, you're stealing from them
和他们的废话
and their horseshit.
消耗 消耗 不停地消耗那些他妈的危险的分分秒秒 好吗
Eat, eat, eat those dangerous fucking minutes. Okay?
-好的  -好吗
-Okay. -Okay?
-当然 好的  -明白了
-You bet. Okay. -Got it.
你们能搞定的 这是小事一桩
You guys got this. It's a cinch.
-好吗  -是的
-Okay? -Yeah.
就照着训练的来
Just let the training kick in.
也许试着享受一下过程
And maybe just try to enjoy it?
嗯 谢谢 格雷格 谢谢
Yeah. Thanks, Greg. Thanks.
-噢 到我们了 伙计们 我们走吧  -好吧
-Oh, we're on, guys. Let's go. -All right,
-开始了 是的  -这就开始了吗
-here we go. Yes. -This is it?
-对 当然  -是时候了
-Right. Sure. -It's time.
-你表现得很棒的  -好的 好的
-You're gonna do great. -Okay. Okay.
-准备好了吗  -好的 过来
-Ready? -Okay. Come here.
-祝大家好运  -你很棒
-Good luck, everybody. -You're good.
-我知道 没事的 好吗  -我们走吧
-I know. Good, yeah? -Let's go.
-我们上吧  -好的
-Let's do this. -All right.
加油 团队
Go team.
商业 科学与运输委员会
The Committee on Commerce, Science and Transportation
即将召开听证会
will come to order.
我们欢迎大家参加今天
We welcome everyone to today's hearing
关于明亮星游轮公司滥用职权行为的听证会
on corporate abuses in the Brightstar cruise lines.
只要看看现金流 我们的价值被低估了
Just look at the cash flow. We are undervalued.
我认为 科技只是让所有人在传统媒体方面
I think tech just had everybody shitting their pants
吓得尿裤子 但是实际上 我们运转得很好
about legacy media, but really, the wheel turns.
而大多数技术都被高估了
And most tech is overvalued.
我们在赚钱 我们是真金白银
We're profitable. We're real money.
这是一个巨大的机会
This is a tremendous opportunity.
这是千载难逢的机会
This is once-in-a-lifetime.
您可以买下最顶端的
You get to buy into the U.S. Media landscape
美国媒体 最顶端的
at the very top. The very top.
好吧 这是一大笔债务 对吧
Well, it's a lot of debt, right?
你确定你能做到吗
Are you sure you can bring it together?
绝对确定以
Absolutely sure.
这位杰米是个他妈的杠杆大师
Jaime here is the fucking master of leverage.
他策划了一些历史上最大的杠杆收购
He has structured some of the biggest LBOs in history.
-对吧  -罪名成立
-Right? -Guilty as charged.
嗯 此外 我们 嗯
Yeah, besides, we'd, um,
持有相当数量的股权
have a decent amount of equity in this
而且 不会有任何的...
and not something of any...
...担心 你好 嗯...他们是你一起的吗
...concern. Hello? Um... Are they with you?
我们...
We...
那个 那个穿黑背心的家伙这里有把枪
The, uh, the guy in the black vest has a gun just here.
戴夫 我们没事 对吧
Dave? We're good, right?
-没事吧  -是的 嘿 听着 我们没事 我们没事
-It's good? -Yeah. Hey, look, we're good, we're good.
-好的  -但是...
-Okay. -But, uh...
我们现在都要和这些先生们一起走 好吗
we're all gonna go with these gentlemen now, okay?
我们都要...走吗
We're all gonna... go?
是的
Yes.
呃...不 我不认为...这是...
Uh... No. I don't think-- Is this--
这些先生们是...究竟是什么人
These gentlemen are-- are who, exactly?
我们和他们一起走 没事的  -戴夫
We'll go with them, it's fine. -Dave?
好吧 呃...戴夫 呃...戴夫...刚刚走出去了
Okay, uh... Dave? Uh... Dave... just walked out.
-戴夫刚刚走出去了  -是的 我们现在和他们一起走
-Dave just walked out. -Yes. We'll go with them now.
好的 我可以问一下这是为什么吗
Okay. Can I just ask what this is in regards to?
这是关于会议的吗 这是...这是生意上的事吗
Is this about the meeting? Is it-- It's a business thing?
-嗯  -好吧 我的安保人员
-Uh-huh. -Okay, and my security guy,
戴夫 他刚刚走出去了 我能问问戴夫去哪儿了吗
Dave, he just walked out. Can I ask where Dave went?
戴夫...戴夫不会来了
Dave-- Dave's not coming.
-噢 戴夫不会来了  -是的 嗯...
-Oh, Dave's not coming. -Yeah. Uh...
嗯...我...我...我真的很想让戴夫过来
Um... I-- I-- I would actually really like for Dave to come.
戴夫在楼下 我们走的时候不会带上他
Dave's downstairs, we'll go without him.
-请吧 先生们  -嗯...戴夫
-Please, gentlemen... -Uh... Dave!
呃...有人对戴夫有点担心
Uh... There's a concern about Dave.
这是安全隐患 所以 我们和这些人合作会更好
It's a security risk here, so we're better with these guys.
好吗 一切都很好 全部都在掌控之中
Okay? It's, uh, all good. Everything is under control.
可能出了状况
There could be a situation,
但幸运的是 我们正在得到照顾
but luckily, we're being looked after.
噢 我们有人照顾 真好
Oh, we're being looked after. That's nice.
莱尔德 我们去...我们去找戴夫
Laird, let's get-- let's get Dave.
-呃...我们得走了  - 是的 噢
-Uh... We need to go. -Yeah. Oh-- Oh!
-礼仪呢 他把我的电话拿走了  -嘿
-Protocol, he took my phone. -Hey!
-而且我无法联系我的安保人员  -好的 好的 好的
-And I can't contact my security. -Yep, yep, yep, yep.
没...没事的 不用担心
It's-- It's fine. Don't worry about it.
伊维斯参议员 您有五分钟的提问时间
Senator Eavis, you have five minutes for questions.
万布斯甘斯先生 我希望我说的正确
Mr. Wambsgans, I hope I'm saying that correctly.
只是一些背景情况 关于莱斯特·麦克林托克先生
Just some background. Mr. Lester McClintock.
他提供工作给那些
You accept he offered jobs
愿意和他一起睡觉的年轻女人 你接受这一点吗
to young women who would sleep with him?
嗯...事情看起来确实是这样
Uh... That does seem to be the case.
嗯...但是公司 嗯 不知道这个情况
Um... But the-- the company, uh, wasn't aware,
而且很显然 那是我之前的事情 嗯...
and obviously, that was some time before my time, um...
但是 比尔...呃 洛克哈特
However, Bill... uh, Lockheart,
我的前任...
my predecessor--
但是 在公司高层和家族成员之间
But within the upper echelons of the firm and the family,
莱斯特通常被称为老莫 对吗
Lester was commonly known as Mo. Is that correct?
我...我不...我不...我...我是一个相对较新的人
I... I don't... I don't... I-- I'm a relative newcomer.
这封邮件里 你称莱斯特·麦克林托克为"老莫" 为什么
This email, you call Lester McClintock "Mo." Why?
我...我觉得这只是个昵称吧
I-- I guess I think it was just a nickname.
嗯 你在给家人和同事的电子邮件中称他为"老莫"
Mm-hm. You call him "Mo" Over 30 times in emails
超过30次 但是 你在发给他的私人邮件里
to family and colleagues, but you never use it
从来没有这样称呼过他
in the items of correspondence sent to him privately,
比如 在他生病期间 为什么不这样称呼他
for instance, during his illness. Why not?
-参议员 我不知道  -你不知道吗
-Senator, I don't know. -You don't know?
他被称为老莫 但是总是在背后被人这样称呼
He was called Mo, but always behind his back.
嗯...嗯...我得...我必须得看一下电子邮件
Um... Uh... I'd-- I'd have to look at the emails,
嗯 我从未想过这个事
uh, I never thought about it.
莱斯特的昵称是老莫 莫-莱斯特 性骚扰者
Lester's nickname was Mo. Mo Lester. Molester.
从来没有联想到过吗
That never came up?
参议员 我想 呃...
Senator, I think, uh...
我想他也许 有一点儿令人毛骨悚然
I guess maybe he was, uh, a little creepy-seeming perhaps.
好吧 你当时在公司任职
Well, you were right there.
不过 不能因为我们...他被称为 莫-莱斯特
But just because we-- he was called, um, Mo Lester,
就说明他...
doesn't-- didn't mean...
这只是...这只是一个庸俗的笑话而已
It was just a-- It's just an off-color joke.
你明白吧
You know?
那个称呼完全是100％的事实
That was 100 percent based on truth.
但是 所有这么这么多叫他"性骚扰者"
But of all the many, many people who called this molester...
"莫-莱斯特"的人里面 没有一个人有丝毫的想法
"Mo Lester," Not one of them had the slightest idea
认为他真的是个性骚扰者
that he actually was a molester.
我的意思是 你可以看得出来 这能让人轻易信服吗
I mean, you could see how that stretches our credulity.
是的 参议员 我可以看得出来
Yes, senator, I can see that.
我想 他似乎看起来有点像 也许吧
I think he just seemed a bit like one, maybe.
但是 我们一无所知
But we didn't know anything.
好吧 如果他看起来有点像
Well, if he seemed a little bit like one,
你难道不认为负责人有必要
don't you think it behooved the people in charge
-查清楚他是不是这样的人...  -噢 我的...
-to find out if he was one... -Oh, my...
...在再把他派到满是年轻女性
...before you sent him out on ships full of young women
和弱势的老年与年轻客人的船上去吗
and vulnerable old and young guests?
噢 他妈的 噢 他妈的 他妈的 他妈的
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck!
这不是生意 对吧
This isn't business, is it?
不 这完全不是生意
No, it is not very businessy.
妈的
Oh, shit!
-嘿  -别担心 一切都很正常
-Hey. -Don't worry, this is all normal.
嗯 太好了 因为这让人感觉超级他妈的正常 伙计
Yeah, great, 'cause this feels super fucking normal, man.
这是...这些人是恐怖分子吗
Is this-- Are these terrorists?
我他妈的安全人员在哪 戴夫在哪
And where's my fucking security guy? Where's Dave?
这...只是...
It-- It's just an...
行政行为职能
an administrative action function.
是的 很好 很好 究竟什么是...
Yeah, good, great. And what exactly--
嘿 看那个
Hey, look at that.
在枪口的威胁下 那个家伙不准离开酒店
Guy not being allowed to leave the hotel at gunpoint.
-那是...  -噢 天啦
-That's... -Oh, Christ.
-...行政行为职能  -是的
-...an administrative action function. -Yeah.
-这太...  -什么...什么...行政行为职能是什么
-This is gr-- What-- What-- What is that?
就像...呃...现在这里在聚会
There's just like, uh... um... A gathering here now,
我们和其他...其他一些投资者等等 还有...
of us and some-- some other investors and so on, and...
-还有拿着枪的人 是吗  -是的
-And men with guns, yeah? -Yep, yep.
这些家伙有点像是...
Their guys are some kind of, um...
反腐败的家伙 他们就像...
anti-corruption kind of guys, and they're like...
-这就像是他们组织的会议...  -真的吗
-It's like their conference... -Really?
...或者聚会...
...or, uh, party, and...
我们都被邀请了
we're all invited.
好吧 那很好 嗯...但是 如果我们 你知道吗
Okay, well, that's nice, uh... but what if we, you know,
如果我们...如果我们不想跟他们走怎么办 那样可以吗
what if we-- if we don't wanna go, is that cool?
好吧
Okay.
这是..这是那种你必须去参加的聚会
It's-- It's the kind of party where you have to go.
-噢 我懂了  -不然场面会...很粗鲁
-Oh. I see. -It would be... rude.
好的 好吧 我的意思是
Okay. Well, I mean,
我猜我不介意 有那么...
I guess I don't mind being, like...
...一点点粗鲁
...A little, tiny bit rude.
我想请你注意一下
Let me direct your attention
蓝色标签包的第16号文件
to document 16 of the blue-tabbed packet.
蓝色标签包的...第16号文件
Document 16... of the blue?
-文件表明曾经有...  -第16号文件
-It suggests that there were over... -Document 16.
...四万份电子记录
...forty thousand electronic records
和纸质文件来自于那个时间段
and paper documents from the period
我们对这些文档感兴趣 但是无法获取到
which we're interested in, that were not available to us.
嗯...是的
Uh... Yes,
不幸的是 似乎有很多
unfortunately, it seems that there are a great many
这样的文件
of these documents that were destroyed
在正常的数据管理
in the, uh, course of normal data management
和公司管理过程中被销毁了
and corporate housekeeping.
所以 没有针对性的掩盖吗
So, there was not a targeted cover-up?
硬盘驱动器被清除了也不是吗
The hard drives that were wiped?
嗯...据我所知 这是正常的做法
Uh... It's a normal practice, as I understand it.
嗯...我不是IT专家
Um... I'm not an IT expert.
但是去年的感恩节那天 似乎有很多箱子文件
But on Thanksgiving last year, it seems that a number of boxes
有针对性地专门销毁了
were targeted specifically.
我不知道这件事
I'm not aware of that.
好吧 请你看一下第34项
Well, if you'll look at item 34,
上面显示2918号文件箱到3125号文件箱 ...
it suggests boxes 2918 to boxes 3125...
现在是空的
are now empty.
嗯...而八月份的时候 箱子里装满了文件
Uh... They were full back in August,
但是当这些文件被要求呈交的时候 很显然已经不在了
but when they were subpoenaed, they were apparently unavailable
而在此期间 文件被注销了
and in the interim, they were signed out
请你看一下分类帐15B分组
and if you look at the ledger, packet 15B,
由一个叫格雷戈里·赫希的人记录的
by a Gregory Hirsch.
你认识这个人吗 万布斯甘斯先生
Is that someone known to you, Mr. Wambsgans?
呃...不 不认识 对不起
Uh... No, no, sorry.
-"不认识"  -"不认识"  "不认识"吗 汤姆
-"No"? -"No"? "No," Tom?
噢 是的 是的 很抱歉 是 认识...认识...我认识
Oh, yes, yes, sorry. Yes. Known-- Known-- Known to me.
-认识 从这个意义上来说 认识  -哪个意义
-Yes. In that sense, yes. -In what sense?
嗯...从这个...意义上来说...
Uh... In the sense that, uh...
就是这个 嗯...我明白你的意思...
that, uh... what I understood that you meant--
你认为我是什么意思
What did you think I meant?
那个...我认识他
That-- Um... I knew of him,
但是 不 不 我知道...我知道他 还有他的样子
but no, no, I know-- I know him. And his face.
你知道3月12日凌晨
Do you know what is special
大约3点到5点之间
about the hours between 3:00 a.M. And 5:00 a.M.
-有什么特别之处吗  -呃...不知道 先生
-on the night of March 12th? -Uh... No, sir.
那是你唯一的两个小时时间
That was the only two-hour period in which you did not send
没有在给赫希先生的电子邮件上用这样的标题...
an email to Mr. Hirsch with the title...
"如果不搅碎一些格雷格[鸡蛋] 你就不能成就一个汤姆[做一个煎蛋饼]"
"You Can't Make a Tomlette Without Breaking Some Greggs."
你在一个晚上向他发送了67次同样的电子邮件
You sent the same email to him 67 times in one evening.
我想这是个玩笑
I guess it was a joke.
好的 我很好奇 "人肉家具"
Right. I wonder, do the phrases "Human furniture"
或者"人肉脚凳"这两个词对你来说意味着什么
or "Footstooling" Mean anything to you?
我不知道是什么意思 不知道
Not that I'm conscious of, no.
你有没有把别人当做
Have you ever used another human being
脚凳来使用 万布斯甘斯先生
as a footstool, Mr. Wambsgans?
呃...我...参议员 我使用各种各样的
Uh... I-- Senator, I use a variety of, um,
以目标为导向的激励措施 以提高员工的最佳绩效
target-oriented, um, incentives to enhance optimal performance.
我放弃我剩下的时间
I yield back the balance of my time.
嫁给一个有两个屁眼的男人是什么感觉
What is it like to be married to a man with two assholes?
...很快会再召开
...reconvene shortly.
如果我要给汤姆打一个分数
If I was to give Tom a letter grade,
我会给他一个B+ 代表"糟糕+可怕"
I'd give him a B-plus for "Bad plus terrible."
那全都是...那全都是在针对我
That was all-- That was all fucking me.
他们从各个方面他妈的攻击我
They hit me from every fucking side!
没关系 汤姆 你做得很好
It's okay. Tom, you did good.
噢 我身上没有得到足够的资源
Oh, I didn't get enough resources spent on me.
好吧 这他妈是怎么回事
Okay, what the fuck is going on?
我遭到了...我从各个方向被人操
I'm getting-- I was fucked from every direction!
-你在玩我吗 小西  -汤姆
-Are you fucking me, Shiv? -Tom!
嗯 我是容易上当的人
Huh? I'm the patsy,
-我就是砧板上的肉  -坐下
-I'm the meat in the sandwich. -Sit down.
格丽是防弹武僧 肯德尔和洛根是候补
Gerri is the bulletproof monk. Kendall and Logan in reserve.
我是他妈的砧板上任人宰割的肉
I'm the meat in the fucking sandwich.
嘿 冷静点
Hey, calm down.
噢 他妈的 他妈的 噢 他妈的 噢 他妈的 噢 我操
Oh, fuck. Fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
-好了  -噢 我操
-Okay. -Oh, Fuck.
伙计们 一切都很好 没有发生任何不好的事情
Guys, everything is fine. Nothing bad is happening here.
天啊 噢 我的天啦 啊
Oh, man. Oh, my God. Ah.
操 老天 我刚刚拒绝了十亿的四分之一份额
Fuck, man, I just turned down a quarter of a billion,
现在我要把牢底坐穿了
and now I'm going to jail forever,
因为这个该死的家伙 老天
'cause of this fucking guy, man!
这个该死的...
This fucking-- -
你 出去
You. Outside.
-他  -他妈的滚出去 赶快
-He-- -Out-fucking-side, now!
难以置信
Unbelievable.
小西 有什么办法可以搞清楚
Shiv, is there any way we can find out
会针对我们提些什么问题吗
what's coming down the pipe at us?
因为再出点差错 我们就他妈彻底完蛋了
Because much more of that, and we're fucking toast.
突然之间 桑迪和斯图威...
All of a sudden, Sandy and Stewy are...
在股东看来都成了不错的人选
looking pretty good to the shareholders.
他说得对 也许是时候我们自己研究一下了
He's right. Maybe it's time to drop some of our research.
我会看看我能做点什么
I'll see what I can do.
杰西 你能不能盯着...
Jess, will you keep an eye on...
-你还好吗  -嗯 抱歉
-You? -Okay. Sorry.
真是场闹剧 真他妈是场闹剧
What a shit show. What a fucking shit show.
那... 只是想知道我能不能来打个招呼
So... Yeah. Just wondered if I could say hi.
有谁看到你进来吗
Anyone see you come in?
这些天 你经常上泛美网络
You're pretty regular on ATN these days,
我注意到了 你觉得怎么样
I notice. How are you liking that?
有优点 也有缺点
It's got its advantages, its disadvantages.
他们喜欢收视率
They love the ratings.
是的 对
Yeah, right.
那 我想 我们一起做了那么多事情
So, I feel like after everything we did together,
应该还剩余了一些善意吧
there's some residual good will?
好了 听着 会面结束
Okay, look, meeting over.
我们是不会搞软推销的 小西 很高兴见到你
We're not gonna soft-peddle, Shiv. Great to see you.
我不是在请求 我是在给予
I'm not asking, I'm giving.
-什么  -就帮个忙
-What? -Just a favor.
我们一直在深入调查 我愿意帮忙
We've been digging, and I'd like to help.
我仍然认为吉尔是个很棒的候选人
I still think that Gil is a great candidate,
我不愿意你们愚弄自己
and I would hate for you to make fools of yourselves.
这话可是那个自己老公刚刚被称为
Says the person whose husband was just called,
"一块傻笑的国产羊乳酪"的人说的
"A smirking block of domestic feta,"
-大西洋月刊写的  -韦塞尔 黄鼠狼
-by the Atlantic. -Weissel, the weasel.
你想知道内情吗
You want the dirt?
不 小西 我们不需要你的狗屁背景介绍
No, Shiv, we don't need your shit-talking background briefing
不过 谢谢你
but thank you.
他狡猾得不得了
He's dodgy as fuck.
失去了孩子的共同监护权 有药物滥用问题
Lost joint custody of his kids, substance abuse issues,
因为招妓而被捕
done for soliciting prostitutes.
他不是你的白雪公主
He's not exactly your Snow White,
-他是你的白发魔女  -嗯 没兴趣
-he's your Blow White. -Uh-huh. Not interested.
这次会面从没发生过
This meeting never happened.
好的 在老莫和詹姆斯·韦塞尔上面 你可以花费精力去做
Okay. On Mo and James Weissel, you can go to town.
如果你正在寻找战利品
And if you're looking for a scalp,
我们愿意放弃比尔
we're willing to give up Bill.
所以 如果你想轻松获胜 选择比尔 我们会弃牌
So, if you want the easy win, go for Bill, and we'll fold.
好吗 然后我们可以让泛美网络持续邀请你
Okay? And then we can keep the invites to ATN flowing
我们的舆论攻势会针对你的主要对手
and the snipers trained on your primary rivals.
对不起 告诉你爸这不是针对他
I'm sorry. Tell your dad it's not personal.
我们现在刚刚得到一些非常非常好的东西...
We've just got something really, really good now...
比韦塞尔这事好多了
much better than Weissel.
扯谈 有多好
Bullshit. How much better?
我给你一个线索 其实非常精确地
I'll give you a clue. It actually rhymes
和"你完蛋了"押韵
very precisely with "You're fucked."
这是什么 我们再过一遍
What is it? Let's go through it again.
并没有直接了解到
No direct knowledge.
-并没有直接了解到  -全面合作
-No direct knowledge. -Full cooperation.
好的 嘿嘿 各位 听好了
Okay, hey. Hey. Guys, listen up.
喂 我们出问题了
Hey. We have a problem.
他们本周晚些时候还有其他人作证
They have someone else for later in the week
一个能干掉我们的人
who could probably kill us.
-谁  -等一下
-Who? -Wait a minute.
一个受害者 曾经在莱斯特手下工作
A victim. Used to work under Lester,
以前的娱乐经理 基拉什么的
ex-entertainment manager, Kira someone?
私下也认识一大堆受害者 还了解详细信息
Also knows a bunch of victims personally, and details.
受到个人责任的感召 他们正在让她做好准备
Feels personally responsible. They're prepping her.
-噢 他妈的 我操  -是啊
-Oh, fuck! Fuck! -Yeah.
如果她站出来 保密协议就塌了
If she comes out, and the NDAs domino,
我不认为...我认为就这样了
I don't think-- I think that's it.
嘿 只是想说 "祝我们好运 "
Hey, just wanted to say, "Good luck."
呃...我们要被妖怪伏击了
Uh... We got an incoming bogey.
-她现在在哪儿  -我...我...我只知道这些
-Where is she now? -I-- I-- That's all I know.
噢 他们是通过参议员吉莉亚德找到她的
Oh, uh, they got her through Senator Gilliard,
-你和参议员很熟 对吧 瑞亚  -一点点
-who you know, right, Rhea? -A little.
但是 这是关于什么的
But what is this?
这个 呃...这个假定的受害者
This, uh... This supposed victim.
你认为...有可能吗 我们可以见到...
Do you think-- Is it possible? Could we see--
你知道的 我们可以和她见面吗
You know, could we meet up with her, you know?
谈谈 你知道的 搞清楚她想要什么
Talk? You know, find out what she wants?
-我们道个歉什么的  -什么
-Apologize? -What?
噢 得了吧
Oh, come on.
我们...我们...我们必须试试
We-- We-- We gotta try.
不管是不是真的 这...这都会改变故事的内容
Whether it's true or not, it-- it changes the narrative.
你们俩去一个 你们俩都去 拜托你了
One of you. Both of you. Please.
伙计们 时间快到了 他们正在回去
Guys, it's almost time. They're heading back in.
所以 我们得准备好表演了
So, we gotta get this show on the road.
最后强调一次 以防万一他们直截了当地提问
One last time, just in case they're super-direct,
洛根·罗伊 你有没有在你的游轮上
did you, Logan Roy, witness any assaults
看到过任何袭击 或者参与其中
on your ships or take part in them?
我他妈不会回答这样的问题
I'm not gonna answer a fucking question like that.
-我 呃 我以为只需要直接回答"没有"  -是啊
-I, uh, I thought that's just a "No." -Yeah.
这样的操蛋问题 他妈的休想要我回答
I'm not dignifying that fucking question with an answer.
你们都可以滚蛋了
You can both fuck off.
-好的  -他还好吗
-Okay. -Is he okay?
低血糖
Low blood sugar.
你能给他一个巧克力栓剂吗[堵住他的嘴还是屁股啊?]
Could you, uh, give him a chocolate suppository?
就 呃 在那儿拿个士力架吧
Just, uh, slip a Snickers bar up there?
-唐·格兰德姆  -噢
-Don Grundham. -Oh.
美国竞争研究所
Institute for a Competitive America.
-噢 你好  -继续打好正义之战
-Oh, hello. -Keep fighting the good fight.
这里有很多"康粉"[也可以双关为骗子]在帮你
You got a lot of Con-heads out here pullin' for ya.
-康粉  -是的
-Con-heads? -Yes.
这个说法太妙了 我可以用吗
That's fantastic. May I use that?
-当然  -好的 上帝保佑你 先生
-Sure. -All right, God bless you, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
"康粉" ...
"Con-heads"...
我用我的小眼睛观察一些以H开头的东西
I spy with my little eye something that begins with H.
-人质  -你很聪明
-Hostages. -You are smart,
是吧 好了 刚刚的游戏并没有消耗什么时间
aren't you? Well, that game didn't take us too far.
大概才30秒 玩"结婚 做爱 还是杀人"吗
That was like 30 seconds. Marry, fuck, kill?
结婚 做爱 还是杀人...行政楼层
Marry, fuck, kill... the executive floor.
行政楼层
Executive floor.
那我要杀死雷
I'd kill Ray.
-当然  -和艾尔莎做爱
-Of course. -Fuck Elsa.
和格丽结婚
Marry Gerri.
-格丽吗  -是的
-Gerri? -Yeah.
-和格丽结婚吗  -嗯 选择有限嘛
-Marry Gerri? -Well, it's a small pool.
你要娶格丽吗
You'd marry Gerri?
-你这个恶心的家伙 格丽  -是的
-You sick fuck. Gerri? -Yeah.
你喜欢格丽吗
You like Gerri?
噢 太好笑了 你太他妈恶心了
Oh, that's hilarious. You're fucking disgusting.
居然选格丽
Gerri?
啊 有意思 啊 卡尔 你呢
Ugh! Hot. Ugh! Karl, what about you?
-听着 完全公开吗  -是啊
-Look, full disclosure? -Yeah?
我 嗯 现在正在惊恐发作
I am, um, currently having a panic attack.
我可以坐在那里吗 你介意吗 莱尔德
Could I sit there? Do you mind, Laird?
-行 可以  -真的吗
-Oh, sure. -Really?
-天啦...  -你看上去...没什么不同
-Mm-hm. God... -You seem... kind of the same.
-你好吗 伙计  -是的
-You okay, man? -Yeah.
-你起来吧 站在地上  -噢 好的 噢 老天啊
-Up you go. On the floor. -Oh. Okay. Oh, Jesus.
伙计们
Guys?
你觉得他们要带他们去哪里
Where do you think they're taking them?
看起来他们应该不是去
It doesn't look like they're going
-参加温泉之旅  -噢 他妈的
-for a tour of the spa. -Oh, fuck!
我告诉你...告诉你一些事情
Let me tell you-- tell you something.
-我的建议...  -说吧
-My advice... -Yeah?
....就是什么都不要看
....just don't look at anything.
因为如果你不看 那你就不是目击者
'Cause if you don't look, then you're not a witness.
如果您不是目击者
And if you're not a witness,
-你懂的  -是的 别紧张 伙计
-you know. -Yeah. Just take it easy, man.
放轻松点 你不会...不会有事的
Just take it easy. You don't have-- It's okay.
天啦
God.
-嘿  -噢 我的天啦
-Hey. -Oh, my God.
-嘿  -嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
我们怎么...
How we, uh...
-情况怎么样  -没事 没事 伙计
-How we doin'? -Good. Good, man.
-好的  -都挺好
-Good. -All good.
那 我们总统的女婿要总统
So, uh, my president's daughter's husband has asked him
进一步控制一些关键资产
to take closer control of some key assets.
这是反腐败 但有一点权力攫取
It's anti-corruption, but a bit of a power grab.
在一些土耳其人的默认这下 但这一切都是游戏
Some Turkish acquiescence, but it's all in play.
我能问一下吗 我不是想让这一切都围绕着我们
And can I ask, not to make this all about us,
但是 他们会随时朝我们开枪吗
but are they going to shoot us at any point?
我对这一点也很感兴趣
I'm also intrigued on that point.
不会有人被枪杀
No one is getting shot.
听着 这很复杂 但是 扎纳尔在这里...
Look, it's complicated, but with Zeynal here...
...这笔交易他们有一些利益相关
...there is some interest in the deal.
交易 嗯...好吧 交易 嗯 很好
The deal. Um... Okay, the deal. Yeah. Great.
所以 他们想要弄清楚的一个问题是
So, one query they wanted some clarity on was
我们如何...他们如何确定自己的投资
how could we-- how could they be sure their investment
不会被你们的政府冻结
wouldn't be blocked by your government?
好吧 嗯 不会的 我爸很有影响力
Well, okay, uh, it wouldn't. My father has a lot of sway.
我的意思是 他不能把对手关在酒店里
I mean, he can't lock his opponents up in a hotel,
嗯 但是 好吧 他其实有点可以
uh, but, well, he kinda could.
好吧 呃...你们是另一个出价的
Okay, and, uh... you're the target
-目标  -是的
-of another bid? -Yes.
这难道不是问题吗
Isn't that a problem?
这根本不是问题 如果价钱合适
That is not a problem at all. If the price is right,
我们完全有信心在股东大会之前
we are fully confident that we can reach a settlement
达成和解
before the shareholder meeting.
好的 好吧 进展很顺利
Okay. Okay, well, that went great.
-是的 那...很棒  -真的希望如此
-Yeah. That's... great. -Really hope so.
是的 我的意思是 我们是不是
Yeah. I mean, should we see
应该看看其他人质有没有谁想达成协议的
if any of the other hostages want to cut a deal?
这可能是我们的丰收时刻
This could be a bumper time for us.
好吧 这感觉不太好
Well, this doesn't feel great.
不 不 软技能 女性责任的狗屎工作
No. No, soft skills, lady-duty shit-work.
一点也不好
Not great at all.
参议员 当我读到我的游轮部门
Senators, when I read of the abuses of power
涉嫌滥用职权时...
alleged in my cruise division...
好吧...那是我一生中最糟糕的一天
well... that was the worst day of my life.
因为我想到 坏事可能在我不知情的情况下
To think bad things might have gone on
继续发生
without my knowledge.
坦白说...
And frankly...
我不知道我是否会原谅自己
I don't know if I'll ever forgive myself.
但是我们将进行调查 我们会确保
But we will investigate, and we will make sure
每一个受害者都得到补偿 每一个不法行为...
every victim is compensated, and every act of wrongdoing...
都受到法律的严惩
punished to the full extent of the law.
我只是希望 上帝保佑 你们相信我的话
I just hope, so help me God, you believe me when I say that.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
操 说得好
Fuck, yeah.
伊维斯参议员 下面由你发言
Senator Eavis? Time is yours.
谢谢你 主席女士
Thank you, Madam Chairwoman.
爱默生说过 "每一个机构都是一个人的缩影 "
Emerson said, "Every institution is the shadow of a single man."
在韦斯达 那个人就是洛根·罗伊 不是吗
At Waystar, that man is Logan Roy, isn't he?
好吧 我...
Well, I'm...
我当然不会和爱默生先生争论
I'm certainly not gonna argue with Mr. Emerson.
你的游轮是为了牟利 你的新闻也是为了牟利
Your cruises run for profit, your news runs for profit.
把新闻当做你个人的提款机
Is that any way to keep the life blood
这是让民主的血液
of a democracy going,
继续流动的方法吗
by using news as your own personal ATM?
呃...我...我可以发言吗
Uh... If-- If I may.
嗯...我想你可能有点误解 参议员
Um... I think you might be under a misapprehension, Senator.
在这个国家 所有的新闻媒体
In this country, all news,
从时代杂志到超市小报
from the Times to the supermarket tabloid,
都是为了牟利 先生
is for profit, sir.
我们没有官方媒体 我很确定你知道这一点
We don't have a state media. As I'm sure you know,
要找官媒 你得去中国或者俄罗斯
you'd have to go to China or Russia for that.
-噢 漂亮 狠扇了吉尔一耳光  -我们还没有官方媒体...
-Ooh, snap! Snap on Gil! -We don't have a state media yet...
我们录下来了吗 卡罗丽娜
Have we got that, Karolina?
我们让代理人准备好这句台词
Let's get the surrogates prepped with that line.
他们称吉尔为"疯脑圣人" 因为他很少发表讲话
They call Gil "Meth-Head Santa" Because he so rarely delivers.
我想说的是 在你们的游轮部门
What I'm getting at, is it any surprise
剥削和掩盖行为大行其道
that, uh, exploitation and cover-up runs rife
这有什么稀奇的呢
at your cruise division?
我的意思是 剥削
I mean, exploitation is at
是你们的商业模式的核心
the heart of your business model.
好吧 我...我当然会不同意 但是 呃...
Well, I-- I would, of course, disagree, but, uh...
但是 就过往而言...
but in terms of the historic...
过往...
historical...
过往对玩忽职守的指控...
historic charges of practice-- malpractice, um...
洛根·罗伊先生 你们的游轮部门保留影子日志
Mr. Logan Roy, what did you personally know
以此来混淆不法行为
about the operation of a system of obfuscation
对于这样的制度运作
of wrongdoing in your cruise division...
你个人有什么了解吗
by the means of the keeping of shadow logs?
我相信 那个时候我儿子
At that point, I believe my son was across
-也在参与运营 对吧  -哪个时候
-that operation, right? -At which point?
他负责娱乐运营的时候
At the point he was across entertainment operations.
你可以和他说
You can talk to him.
那 肯德尔·罗伊先生
Mr. Kendall Roy, then.
-告诉我们有关影子日志的事情  -好的 你知道吗
-Tell us about the shadow logs. -Okay, you know what,
对不起 主席女士 我...我可以说一会吗
I'm sorry, Madam Chairwoman, can-- can I speak for a moment?
因为你知道吗 我...我今天真诚地来到这里
Because you know, I-- I'm here in good faith today,
我很愿意和你谈谈 参议员 和委员会
I'm very willing to talk you, Senator, and this committee
谈谈我们的运营 但是 我们废话少说吧
through our operations, but, uh, let's cut the BS,
好吗 因为在我看来 这项调查
shall we? Because it seems to me that this investigation,
嗯 不是关于游轮行业的
uh, is not about proper oversight
规范和标准的适当的监督
of cruise industry codes and standards,
或是某件二十年前的非常令人遗憾
or some highly regrettable but isolated incidents
但是孤立的事件
from nearly two decades ago.
这项调查给我的感觉是
What this feels to me it's about
你个人不喜欢我父亲
is your personal dislike of my father,
你对他的报纸和他的新闻频道
and your ideological hatred of his newspapers
尤其是 泛美网络的成功故事
and his news channels, and in particular,
充满了意识形态的仇恨
of the, uh, success story which is ATN,
然而 在过去四个月里 你在泛美网络
on which you've appeared, I think, 14 times
我想 应该是出现过14次 参议员
in the last four months, Senator.
好 好 好
Good, good, good.
伊维斯参议员 在我看来
Senator Eavis, it seems to me
既然你在意识形态上不认同我们
that since you don't agree with us ideologically,
我们说再多都没用
that nothing we can say will be enough,
再卑躬屈膝也不够
no groveling will be low enough,
而且尽管你很想指责我们有偏见
and as much as you like to accuse us of bias,
但是 今天 你才是那个带着偏见的人
uh, today, you're the one with the bias.
所以 我想说 继续吧 尽你所能打击我们好了
So, I say go ahead. Hit us as hard as you can.
我们可以接受 我们没有什么可隐藏的
We can take it. We have nothing to hide.
那 她在等我们 是吗
So, she's expecting us, yeah?
听着 我不会进去的
Look, I'm not going in.
说真的吗 你要...你要让我独立面对吗
Seriously? You're... You're leaving it to me?
西沃恩 你也不必这样做
Siobhan, you don't have to do this.
如果她要去作证 而且引人注目...
If she speaks and she's compelling...
那我家族的公司就完蛋了
then that's it for my family's company.
所以...是的 我确实必须去
So... yeah. I do have to.
谢谢 瑞亚
Thanks, Rhea.
非常感谢你的发言
Thank you so much for your time.
啊 罗伯茨先生 我们现在可以悄悄灌输一点
Ah, Mr. Roberts. We can now slip into something
一点稍微舒适的内容了
a little bit more comfortable.
我已经感觉好多了
I already feel better.
我想立即说一声 郑重声明 两位……
And I want to say right off, for the record, gentlemen...
我喜欢你们
I like you.
我想和你们俩一起喝一杯
I'd like to have a drink with both of you.
我和我妻子曾经一起乘坐过你的其中一条游轮
And I have taken one of your cruises with my wife
坦率地说 那是令人愉快的旅程
and it was, frankly, delightful.
好的 谢谢您 参议员 您真是和气
Well, thank you, Senator, that's very kind.
不 不 小心
No, no. Careful!
嗨 你好 我是西沃恩·罗伊 谢谢你见我
Hi. Hi, Shiv Roy. Thank you for seeing me.
我只是想找个机会来打个招呼
I just wanted the opportunity to say hello.
我想说 我意识到
And I want to say I realize
这是一个难以想象的困难情况
this is an incredibly difficult situation,
所以我...我希望你知道 我深深地感谢你
so I-- I want you to know I deeply appreciate you
-花时间  -对 嗯...
-taking the time. -Right. Um...
我不确定我应该...我...我以为这会是一次
I'm not sure I should-- I-- I thought this was gonna be
和瑞亚的非常私人的会面
a very unofficial thing with Rhea?
嗯 是的
Uh-huh. Yeah.
嗯...这感觉很不一样
Uh... This feels very different.
不 她很忙 嗯...但是她稍后会加入
No, she's busy. Uh... But she will join later on.
-我...  -对我...我...
-I-- -Right. I j-- I--
我只是不知道我会不会感到不舒服
I just don't know if I feel comfortable.
噢 但是我不是来这里阻止你去作证的
Oh, but I'm not here to stop you testifying.
-当然  -嗯 而且我不是来这里给你提任何条件的
-Sure. -Yeah. And I'm not here to offer you anything.
我是来这里倾听 尝试理解你的
I'm here to listen, and to try to understand.
只是想了解我们做错了什么以及如何补救
Just trying to understand what we did wrong and how I can fix it.
好吧 这个时间出现 想要了解情况...
Well, it's a very convenient time to show up...
-也太巧了吧  -噢...
-wanting to understand. -Oh...
-我觉得你很勇敢  -好的 谢谢
-I think you're brave. -Well, thank you.
亲爱的 不 不 下来不要爬太高
Honey, no. No, get down. Don't go too high.
过来 过来
Come here! Come here!
什么 噢 我的天啦 啊
What? Oh, my God! Ah!
我们来了
There we go!
噢 哇 这高跟鞋疼死我了
Oh, wow. These just kill me.
深有体会 过来...
I know. Come on...
你知道吗 这样 嗯...
You know, look, um...
我的...我爸...我爸在几个月前
My-- My dad... My dad, a couple months ago,
你知道吗 他把我忽悠了
you know, he screwed me over.
他给了我一个不真实的提议
He made me an offer that wasn't real.
而且他是个连环骗子
And he's a serial liar.
而我会很坦率地和你谈
And I'm gonna be very frank with you,
不玩任何花招 我不信任他 好吗
put my cards on the table, I don't trust him. Okay?
在你们公司上班一直很艰难
Your firm has been very tough.
是的 太他妈对了
Yeah, too fucking right.
-骚扰吗  -是的
-Harassment? -Yeah.
晚上来检查 上班时也出现
Visits at night, turning up at work.
奇怪的电子邮件内容 我的意思是 我...我...不是想指责你...
Weird email stuff. I mean, I-- I... don't want to accuse you--
不 这完全有可能
No, it's perfectly possible.
是的 我的意思是 安保是外包的
Yeah, I mean, it's out-sourced security,
所以 谁...谁知道会发生什么呢
so who... Who knows what could be happening?
有可能比你想像的还要糟糕
It's probably worse than you think.
-是的 是的  -是的
-Yeah. Yeah. -Yeah.
不过 嘿 你现在应该安全了
But hey, you should be safe from all that now.
你现在掌握了主动权 现在 他们害怕了
You've got the whip hand. Now, they're scared.
我不觉得那样的事情还会再发生在你身上了
I don't think that stuff will happen to you anymore.
你不觉得
You don't think?
老实说 我不知道
Being honest, I don't know.
但是...那样看起来会很糟
But... it would look bad.
你已经破级别了 你现在属于新类别
You've broken ranks, you're in a new category.
但是 听着...我想整顿这些
But, look... I wanna clean up.
我需要了解所有这些情况
I need it all out there.
-当然  -是的 不 我真的想这么做
-Sure. -Yeah, no, I do.
我想开除这些混蛋 我希望你能帮助我
I wanna fire these bastards. And I want you to help me.
当然
Sure.
好吧 我想 你知道吗
Well, I guess, you know,
我唯一想问你的问题是...
the only question I would have for you is just...
这是...这是 这是正确的论坛吗
is this-- this, you know, the-- the right forum?
好的 终于说到正题了
Okay, here it comes.
不 实话实说 问一个更好的问题
Nope, honestly? A better question.
你真正希望发生的是什么
What do you actually want to happen?
我想让人们知道莱斯特是什么样的人
I want people to hear what Lester was like.
他是怎么对待我和其他女人的
How he treated me and other women.
我希望能发表休森的故事
I want the Hewson story to come out.
她是怎么落水的...以及当时没有任何营救的努力
How she went overboard... and there was no rescue attempt,
因为他们以为是一个偷渡者
because they thought it was a stowaway.
"无真人参与"
"No real person involved."
对
Right.
嘿 你想坐下吗
Hey, you want to sit down?
我的意思是 好事情是
I mean, the good thing is,
会有很多人站在你这边
you're gonna have a lot of people on your side.
他们会...他们会呼喊着你的名字 支持你 然后...
Who will-- Who will sing your name, and back you up, and...
是的
Yeah.
但是其他人呢 你知道的 另一边的人
But the other people? You know, the other side?
普通人 他们会质疑你
Normal people, they will doubt you.
他们会说...很难听的话
They'll say... terrible things.
他们会称你为荡妇...
They'll call you a slut...
称你为妓女 财迷
and a whore, and a money-grubber.
你的生活将会四分五裂
Your life is gonna get ripped apart.
你的家 你会想搬走
Your home, you'll want to move out.
有那么两三天 你会变得有点出名
For two or three days, you're gonna be kind of famous,
但随后 喧嚣会渐行渐远失去关注
but then the caravan moves on.
我只是觉得这是我必须做的
I just think it's what I have to do.
是啊 没错 不 我明白了 那很好
Yeah, true. No, I get it. That's good.
但是从明天开始 那将是……你的未来
But from tomorrow, that's... all you'll ever be.
对于你的孙子 对于你在假期遇到的人来说
To your grandkids, to the people you meet on vacation.
当他们用谷歌搜寻的时候 对吧
When they google you, yeah?
一页又一页的污秽和谎言
Pages and pages of filth and lies.
你讣告的第一行 最后一行
First line of your obituary. Last line.
所以 你想要得到什么
So, what is it that you are trying to get?
钱吗 你可以得到钱
Because money? Money you can have.
这很容易 幕后交易 采访中露面
That's easy. Book deal. Interview appearances.
我们可以给你几百万美元...
We will give you millions of dollars...
而且我会消灭那些干这种卑鄙勾当的人
and I will destroy the men who ran that dirty operation.
我会因为他们的所作所为毁掉他们
I will kill them for what they've done.
我希望你能帮我
And I want you to help me.
因为你 我们会成为世界上最好
We will be the best, cleanest operation in the world
最干净的运营 如果你帮我实现这一点
because of you, if you help me do this.
你能帮我吗
Would you help me?
好吧 这...这听起来...
Well, it-- it sounds...
我可以信任你吗
Can I trust you?
不 不 实际上 不可以
No. No, actually, no.
基拉 你现在卷入了一场利益冲突的风暴
Kira, you're in a shitstorm of conflicting interests here.
你不能相信任何人 你只需要聪明一点
You can't trust anyone. You just have to be smart.
所以 请听取每个人的意见然后进行评估
So, listen to everyone and make an assessment.
因为 坦率地说 我想要对我最有利的结果
'Cause frankly, I want what's best for me.
但是其他人呢
But the other people?
那些希望你明天去那里作证
The folks who want you to get up there tomorrow,
让你的生活四分五裂的人 他们想要对他们最有利的东西
and get pulled apart? They want what's best for them.
你需要考虑对你最有利的东西 对吧
You need to think about what's best for you, huh?
嘿 罗曼
Hey, Roman.
-什么  -醒醒
-What? -Wake up.
嘿
Hey!
-都好吗 伙计 一切都好吗  -都好 都好
-Good, man, good? -All good. All good.
你好 嗨 我很抱歉
Hello. Hi. I'm so sorry.
外籍人士
Foreign nationals,
-请表明你们的身份  -噢 我的天啦
-please identify yourselves. -Oh, my God.
-噢 我操  -你怎么看
-Oh, fuck. -What do you think?
嗯...我不知道 我觉得传统上
Uh... I don't know. I feel like, traditionally,
美国人通常在这一点上表现不佳
Americans don't usually fare well at this point.
我不知道 你怎么想 卡尔
I don't know, what do you think, Karl?
-噢 他妈的  -按他说的去做
-Oh, fuck. -Just do what he says.
好的 嗯...
Yeah, okay. Um...
-罗曼·罗伊吗  -对
-Roman Roy? -Yup.
请跟我来
Follow me, please.
-祝你好运  -嗯...
-Good luck. -Yeah. Uh...
也祝你好运
Good luck to you, too.
-加油 赫斯队  -加油 赫斯队
-Go, Hi-- Hearts. -Go, Hearts.
无论如何 谢谢你的支持
Anyway, thank you for your support.
应该的 随时支持
You got it. All the time.
-你好  -干得漂亮
-Yes? -Great job.
-谢谢  -我向你致敬
-Thank you. -I salute you.
-谢谢你 参议员  -干得很棒
-Thank you, Senator. -Excellent job.
-谢谢  -优秀
-Thank you. -Excellent.
-说得好  -干杯 比尔
-Here, here. -Cheers, Bill.
干得真棒
Well done.
很高兴和团队重新建立联系
Lovely to reconnect with the gang.
感谢你的支持 比尔
I appreciate your support, Bill.
你开玩笑吧 这么多美好回忆
Are you kidding? So many memories, huh?
我应该写一本书 我可以写 我一直在记日记
I should write a book. I could. I've got the diaries.
但是没时间写 没时间
But no time. No time!
你还好吗
You okay?
-你...干得很棒  -谢谢
-You... did great. -Thank you.
肯定非常难 但是你做到了 她退出了
It must've been tough, but you did it, she dropped out.
"私人原因" 是的 你做得很棒
"Personal reasons." Yeah, you did good.
谢谢
Thank you.
那 你还好吗 孩子
So, are you okay, kiddo?
是的 嗯 很好
Yeah. Yeah, good.
你 呃...你感觉...感觉还好吗
You, uh... You feeling-- feeling okay?
我 嗯...如果当时场面难堪 我很抱歉
I'm, uh... I'm sorry if it was rough.
不 很好 我们很好 一切都很好
No, it was... it was fine. We're good. It's all good.
喂 洛根 瑞亚在这里 但她...她想单独说几句
Hey, Logan? Rhea's here, but she-- she wants a word.
好的
Okay.
-你还记得娜奥米·皮尔斯吗  -是的
-You remember Naomi Pierce? -Yeah,
-嗯  -她大老远来这里...
-yeah. -She came down to--
-嗨  -...支持我们
-Hi. -...to support us.
那 如你所知 我没有进去
So, as you know, I didn't go in.
嗯 嗯 不 没事 小西很厉害
Yeah, yeah. No, it's fine. Shiv's tough.
听着 你能告诉我发生了什么事吗
Look. Will you tell me what happened?
你什么都可以问我
You can ask me anything.
不 我不知道该问什么 你告诉我
No. I don't know what to ask. You tell me.
好吧 这都是...你知道的
Well, it's all... You know.
很久以前的事了
It goes a long way back.
你...你以前有没有让编辑
Did you-- Did you ever have an editor
用手帮你举着毛衣
who put a hand up a sweater?
那 以前的办事风格不太一样
Well, things were done differently in those days.
我不能毫不知情地管理公司
I can't fly blind.
莱斯特·麦克林托克是你的朋友吗
Was Lester McClintock a friend of yours?
不 我不认为他是我的朋友 不是
No, I wouldn't say he was a friend, no.
你曾经告诉我 他是一位密友
You once told me he was a close friend.
-你告诉我的  -好吧...
-You told me that. -Well...
朋友 密友 同事 我也说不清楚
Friend, close friend, colleague, I don't know.
这算是...一种超能力 对吧
It's kind of a-- a superpower, isn't it?
当着别人的面撒谎而若无其事
If you can lie to someone like that, to their face.
我的意思是 我知道你在说谎
I mean, I know you're lying,
但是我还是觉得你说得很合理 而且很吸引人
but I still find you very plausible and appealing.
我词不达意
I misspoke.
嗯
Uh-huh.
原谅我
Forgive me.
但是 有些事情就是会时不时地发生
But there are some things that went on from time to time,
而我只是想保护你
and I just wanted to protect you.
-我不需要你的保护  -嗯 你知道吗 作为下一任总裁
-I don't need your protection. -Well, you know, as the next CEO,
避开某些区域可能比较明智
it might be wise to keep clean of certain areas.
我一直在想这事
I've been thinking about that.
我不确定能不能继续这样下去
I'm not sure it works any longer.
那 你想要什么
So, what do you want?
我不确定自己想为你工作
I'm not sure I want to work for you.
很好 你让我感到震惊
Fine, you've got me over a barrel.
你知道这点 我知道这点 所以告诉我 你想要什么
You know it, I know it, so tell me what you want
-然后我们来谈谈  -你没搞明白
-and let's get into it. -You don't understand.
我退出了 我不想成为这其中一份子
I'm out. I don't want to be part of this.
噢 得了吧 别扯谈了
Oh, come on. Fuck off!
"一本正经"小姐
Little Miss Prim.
你知道的
You knew.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
我认为情况已经变了 在细节方面
I think it's changed. In the details.
你不需要去经历细节
You don't walk over details.
池子的底部深不可测
I can't see the bottom of the pool.
我...我...我不知道你是否还在乎什么
I-- I-- I don't know if you care about anything.
-这让我感到害怕  -噢 是的
-And that scares me. -Oh, yeah.
该死的语言 该死的表达 拜托 留下来
Fucking words. Fucking words. Come on. Stay!
我总是能找到其他人的
I could always find someone else.
你知道你可以被人替代
You know you're fungible.
-我无可替代  -噢 是的 你可以被替代
-I am not fungible. -Oh, yes, you are.
你他妈的可以被随意替代
You're as fungible as fuck.
好吧
Fine.
那我替代我好了 来吧 试试
Then funge me. Go ahead. Try.
瑞亚
Rhea.
今天 肯德尔·罗伊给参议院商务委员会
Kendall Roy served self-satisfied hypocrites
那些自欺欺人的伪君子们送上了一份现实派的健康部分
on the senate commerce committee a healthy portion of reality pie
他把他们打了个落花流水
today when he delivered them a takedown for the ages.
委员会里的民主党人对这家...
Democrats on the committee had worked themselves...
-那...  -...历史悠久的公司
-So... -...into a fit of phony outrage
-产生了一阵虚假的愤怒  -瑞亚走了吗
-over historic corporate... -Rhea's gone?
-但是他们做出了致命的错误估计  -是的
-But they made a fatal miscalculation. -Yep.
她无法克服这种仇恨
She can't hack the hate.
好吧 那她可以滚蛋
Well, she can fuck off
在一家他妈的电话公司
and enjoy her lily-white, chicken-flesh conscience
享受她"纯洁无瑕" 的圣母心了
working for a fucking phone company.
是的 是的 也许吧
Yeah. Yeah, well, maybe.
是的 但是 你觉得这就完了吗
Yeah, but do you think that's it?
如果基拉不作证 而且我们牺牲掉比尔 你认为我们渡过难关了吗
If Kira holds, and we kill Bill, do you think we're through?
老实说吗
Honestly?
不行 股东大会是道坎
No. Not with the shareholders.
恐怕肯德尔的这套话行不通
I'm afraid this Kendall stuff won't play.
他们更像是...他妈的素食主义者
They're a little more... fucking vegetarian.
-不行吗  -不行
-No? -No.
是的  是的
Yes. Yes.
他像个战士一样 但我很受伤
He came out like a fighter, but I'm hurt.
我们很受伤
We're hurt.
比尔只是演习  他不会善罢甘休的
And Bill's on maneuvers. He won't go quietly.
不不不  比尔不是答案
No, no, no. Bill's not the answer.
我们需要更高层的人
We need something big.
是的...
Yeah...
献血的时候到了
Time for a blood sacrifice.
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠